<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kanishka Misra</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kanishka Misra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Population growth and Doubling times with tidyverse</title>
      <link>/2018/population-growth-and-doubling-times-with-tidyverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/population-growth-and-doubling-times-with-tidyverse/</guid>
      <description>Roses are red, violets are blue
  This is a forced rhyme, here’s blog post two!
 Background Ever since I worked on data about populations at my internship at Perscio, a healthcare data analysis firm in Indianapolis, as well as worked with a Professor of Demography and Social Policy on a paper about demographic data, I have gained interest in population problems - mostly through readings.
The best way to restart this journey would be to do so using what population problems often involve: Data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attitudes of employees towards mental health in the tech workplace</title>
      <link>/2018/osmi-mental-health-in-tech-survey-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/osmi-mental-health-in-tech-survey-data/</guid>
      <description>Understanding and accepting mental health as an issue at the workplace has become ever so crucial in recent times. Mental illnesses like depression and anxiety can have a significant economic impact; the estimated cost to the global economy is US$ 1 trillion per year in lost productivity (source). Open Sourcing Mental Illness (OSMI) is a non profit organization that focuses on raising awareness, education and providing resources to support mental wellness at workplaces, especially in the tech industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Post</title>
      <link>/2017/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Why? I feel no other content can do enough justice to a blog’s first post than the one describing why the author would take out time from his/her daily routine and write about stuff. So lets start with the why:
Over the course of my undergraduate degree at Purdue, I have increasingly grown fond of the R programming language as part of my journey in a data driven career. The community surrounding the open-source language is one of the main reasons why I believe R has become so popular in data projects as well as data science teams in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>